Hi, everyone.
FOLLOW MY VOICE
1. GO OUT INTO THE WORLD
Hi
How are you?
Who is this?
Kang
Kang? From Follow My Voice?
Of course hahaha
How many Kangs do you know?
Sorry for bothering
I love the picture you sent me
I noticed it was signed with a K
Did you paint it?
Yes
That's so cool!
But… Hang on! How do I know it's you?
I'M NOT GOING TO GET BETTER
I'M NEVER GOING TO LEAVE THE HOUSE
I'M ALONE
I CAN'T BREATHE
IT'S A PANIC ATTACK
I'M GOING TO DIE
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
IT'S KANG
HE'S GOING TO KNOW THAT I'M SICK
I CAN'T BREATHE
I'M NOT OKAY
KANG, PLEASE HELP ME
2. BUILD YOUR DAILY LIFE
Hi, Min Seo!
Brother!
Come on, don't get distracted.
You got this wrong.
Dad, we made a mistake!
Let me see.
Well…
Your brother had better help you.
Yeah, I'd better.
This isn't your thing either.
When will you guys stop arguing?
We weren't arguing.
It's always the same.
Don't worry about that.
Let's keep drawing…
Hi, folks!
For… Klara
NEW TALENT
COMPETITION
How was your day?
I'm stuck because of the snow
Where can we see each other alone?
3. DARE TO FEEL
I missed you. Always stay by my side.
Don't leave me.
Hold me. I love you. Tae-ho.
FACETIME VIDEO
KANG
Luckily, we did those tests
after your mother's illness.
There's always a genetic risk.
I'm waiting for you in the car
'Cause it's freezing
It's orange
A little old
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I had to leave
Another time
Is everything okay?
Dad, am I making too much noise?
No, not at all. I like your song.
I think you're going to win.
Kang, I'm here.
If there's anything
you want to talk about, I'm here for you.
Thanks.
beautiful but sad,
this show today Sigue mi voz
is pretty sad
that's how I ended up
4. LEARN TO LOVE YOURSELF
DON'T WORRY…
THINK ABOUT SOMETHING PRETTY
Hi, everyone.
I WILL HAVE A HAPPY ENDING
I pictured you differently
But I like you better this way
With highlights in your hair
And eyes the color of the sea
The summers will pass
We'll grow older
You'll meet some guy
He'll write you better songs
And someday
I'll be a beautiful memory
And all that will remain of this love
Is a whisper in your ear
If your heart races
And you look strange in the mirror
Even if you can't see anything
Follow my voice
There is no darkness
That can't be made light
5. FOLLOW YOUR VOICE
5. FOLLOW MY VOICE